{"status":"Success","data":{"quiz_datas":[{"question_no":"698","question":"\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u200c \u0d05\u0d24\u0d4d\u200c\u0d32\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u200c \u0d30\u0d02\u0d17\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d1c\u0d40\u200d\u0d35\u0d4d\u200c \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u200c \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d\u200c \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d30\u0d02\u0d17\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u200c \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d?","option1":"\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2b\u0d4d\u200c\r\n","option2":"\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u200c","option3":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c","option4":"\u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"120","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d ","option2":"\u0d24\u0d43\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d42\u0d7c","option3":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 ","option4":"\u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d42\u0d7c ","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"63","question":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d35\u0d48\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d35\u0d48\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d39\u0d02","option2":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d35\u0d48\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d26\u0d40\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d","option3":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d35\u0d48\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d21\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d","option4":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d35\u0d48\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d31\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d3f","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"356","question":"\u0d05\u0d30\u0d3f, \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d, \u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a, \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d28, \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d40 \u0d2d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2d\u0d35\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d37\u0d15\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d","option1":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d28\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e","option2":"\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d15\u0d02","option3":"\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d1c\u0d02","option4":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d34\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"636","question":"2014-\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d3f","option1":"\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c","option2":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d02 ","option3":"\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30","option4":"\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d3f","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"221","question":"\u2018\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u2019 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d02","option2":"\u0d38\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d02","option3":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d02","option4":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d02","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"55","question":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d23\u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d47\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d\u200c ?","option1":"\u0d1c\u0d3f.\u0d36\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d","option3":"\u0d28\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41","option4":"\u0d07.\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"568","question":"\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d20\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d16\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3f","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d1c\u0d3f","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d21\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d1c\u0d3f","option4":"\u0d13\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d1c\u0d3f","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"354","question":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d","option1":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d02\u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d32","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d32","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d31","option4":"\u0d07\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d02","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"609","question":"\u0d38\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d42\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d","option1":"\u0d0e\u0d02.\u0d06\u0d7c. \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d7c","option2":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d7c","option3":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d7c","option4":"\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d36\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d7c","answer":"1"}]},"code":"100"}
